(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.2",
"generated_at": "2026-08-28T18:07:50.492324",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
2022/1/30 21:00 3DLIVE #尾丸ポルカ生誕祭
[Omaru Polka Birthday Festival - 2022/1/30 21:00 3DLIVE]
本日は「目指せ！最強アイドル決勝戦」にご来場いただき、誠にありがとうございます。
Thank you very much for attending today's "Aim for the Strongest Idol Finals."
ライブビューイングの方に向けても、開演に先立ちまして、お願い申し上げます。
We have a request for those watching via live viewing prior to the start of the show.
ライブビューイングの方は、どなたでも声を上げる行為、ペンライトなどを振る行為は制限されていません。
Those watching via live viewing are not restricted from cheering or waving penlights.
Twitterのハッシュタグは「#尾丸ポルカ誕生日2022」でつぶやいてください。
Please tweet using the Twitter hashtag "#OmaruPolkaBirthday2022".
Twitterのハッシュタグは「#尾丸ポルカ生誕祭」でつぶやいてください。
Please tweet using the Twitter hashtag "#OmaruPolkaBirthFest".
スクリーンショットの撮影も自由となっております。
Taking screenshots is also permitted freely.
フォロワーリーナにおいでのお客さまは、お席について今しばらくお待ちください。
Guests in the follower arena, please take your seats and wait a moment.
本日はご来場いただき誠にありがとうございます。
Thank you very much for coming today.
開演に先立ちまして、ご来場のお客さまにも…
Prior to the start of the show, to our attending guests as well...
開演に先立ちまして、ご来場のお客さまにお願い申し上げます。
Prior to the start of the show, we have a request for our attending guests.
客席内での飲食はご遠慮ください。また、全館禁煙となっております。
Please refrain from eating and drinking in the seating area. Also, the entire building is non-smoking.
携帯電話はアラーム付き時計などはほかのお客さまのご迷惑となりますので、必ず電源をお切りくださいますようご協力をお願いいたします。
Mobile phones, alarm clocks, and the like will disturb other guests, so please make sure to turn off your power.
また、許可の前写真撮影、録音、録画は固くお断りいたします。
Also, photography, audio recording, and video recording without permission are strictly prohibited.
まもなく開演でございます。
The show will begin shortly.
アイドルの頂点が今日、ここに決まる！決勝戦まで勝ち上がってきた尾丸ポルカプロデュースの…
Today, the summit of idols is decided right here! Produced by Omaru Polka, who climbed her way to the finals...
この6人がいったいどんなパフォーマンスを見せてくれるのでしょうか？
What kind of performance will these six show us?
誰が弔う 死地は彼方
Who mourns for us? The deathbed is far away.
静寂を破り 芽吹いた夢を
Breaking the silence, the budding dream—
誓え
Swear it,
穿て
pierce through!
重なる 屍高みへ
Piling up corpses, toward the heights—
届くまで
until it reaches!
吠えろ 徒花
Howl, futile flower!
朽ち果てても進め
Push forward even if you rot away!
奪わせはしない 尊厳の愚弄に
I won't let them take away dignity in mockery,
飢餓を解き放て
unleash the starvation!
枯れても走る ことを命と呼べ
Call running even when withered your very life!
空に叫ぶ 脱・生存の定義
Shout to the sky: the definition of escaping survival!
骨を斬らせて 闇を断て
Offer flesh to sever bone, cut through the darkness!
雲間に光る 三発の勝機
Three chances shining through the clouds—
覚悟を 宿命に突きつけて
thrust your resolve into destiny!
天下に狂い咲く サガ
Blooming madly across the world, the saga!
SAGA
傷ひとつない 手など愚か
Hands without a single scratch are foolish;
意思も自由も その身を投げて
throw your body, will and freedom alike!
守れ
Protect it,
退くな
don't retreat!
涙も 血も 無い 神話を
Until we build a myth with neither tears nor blood—
築くまで
until it is built!
燃えろ 修羅花
Burn, Asura flower!
鼓動亡き 世界で 摂理に抗い 天命も無礼に
In a world without heartbeats, defying providence and even destiny impudently,
腐鎖切り抜けて
break through the rotting chains!
心を無くす ことが死と知れ
Know that losing your heart is death itself!
極めど儚い 偶像の寵児
The transient darlings of idols at their peak—
目には目を剥き 牙を剥け
meet eye for eye and bare your fangs!
目には目を剥き
Strike at the eyes,
牙を剥け
strike with fangs bared!
いつか 誰もが
Someday, everyone will be
散華する捨て石
a scattering stepping stone.
輝け
Shine bright,
刹那無限の火花 乱世に遡る
fleeting infinite sparks, racing into chaotic eras!
SAGA
何が 神の冒涜か
What could be a desecration of the gods?
裁きなどさせない
There is no room for judgment!
希望 高らかに打ち鳴らせ
Ring out hope high above,
呼吸よりも生きた証
a proof of life greater than mere breath!
徒花
Bloom, adabana!
朽ち果てても進め 奪わせはしない
Even if withered, press forward! I won't let you take it!
尊厳の愚弄に 飢えを解き放て
Unleash the starvation of foolish dignity,
枯れても走る ことを命と呼べ
call running even when withered your life!
空に叫ぶ 脱・生存の定義
Cry out to the skies, the definition of survival and escape.
骨を断らせて 闇を断て
Let bone cut bone, slash through the darkness!
雲間に光る 篡奪の勝機
Shining in the clouds, the victory of plunder,
覚悟を宿命に突きつけて
thrust your resolve into destiny!
荒野を駆ける 乱性に挑む
Charging into the chaos of the wildlands,
天下に狂い咲く
blooming madly across the world!
SAGA
不意に question mark が絡みつくわ
Question marks get tangled up unintentionally,
けど selfish sign も踊り出すわ
yet even a selfish sign starts to dance.
ココロ 天秤 の ご機嫌 どうでしょう ねぇ
How are you doing, mood of the scales of the heart?
瞬間 じゃ 決まらない 思考回路 左右 ふわふわ 不安 回廊
In an instant, there's no deciding, thought circuits left and right, unsteady anxiety corridors.
a to z に 隙 は 無い し 至って だって 選定 easy ?
There are no gaps from a to z, going so far as to select easy?
軽く 言わ ない で よね 僕は 僕の 都合 も ある から
Don't say it so lightly, I have my own circumstances too—
とは 言って も そろそろ ok … ok ?
well, even so, pretty soon it's okay... okay?
あのね i like me は 確定 事項 でも
You know, "I like me" is a settled fact,
i know me は 言い切れ ない
yet "I know me" I can't quite say for sure.
ためらっても 論 より 証拠 悩んだ 時間 を 自信 に 変換 し て
Even if we stall, evidence over theory, converting troubled time into confidence.
絶えないで 変わっていく 世界 の いたずら
The mischief of a world that keeps changing without end,
パラレル みたい に 浮かんで くる ひとりごと
floating like a parallel world, one by one.
僕 が いつか そうだ 大人 に なる まで
Until I someday grow up to be an adult,
交わさなく たって も いい でしょ ？
isn't it fine to just make unkept promises?
ほら 一歩 踏み出す タイミング 狙い撃ち
Look, aiming and striking the timing of taking that first step,
願い を 起動 する 呪文 が 必要 な ん です
we need an incantation to activate the wish.
i want to change ぐらい なら 言っちゃおう かな yeaaah
I want to change—if I'm gonna say it, maybe I'll just blurt it out!
飽きてる 暇 も ない ほど yeaaah
Yeah, with not even enough time to be bored,
奏でる よ pretty fever !
yeah, we can play it—pretty fever!
i think so ねぇ このままじゃ 完成度 上げられないまま time goes on
I think so, you know, just like this, completion level can't be raised, time goes on.
そう 幻 じゃ ない でしょ わがまま
Yes, it's not an illusion, self-will.
周り が 認めてる プロフィール と 目指す 未来図 の 純粋度
The profile recognized by those around us and the purity of the future we aim for.
ああ 足して 2 で 割って そのぐらい は 見逃して ！
Ah, add them, divide by two, just overlook that much!
question mark が絡みつくわ
Question marks get tangled up,
けど selfish sign も踊り出すわ
yet even a selfish sign starts to dance.
ココロ 天秤 の 裁きは 決まってる の
The judgment of the scales of the heart is already decided.
不器用に回ってる 世界 も 好きだよ
I love a world that turns out a bit clumsy,
それでも 器用に 浮かんで くる ひとりごと
yet even so, floating skillfully, each and every one of us.
困らせちゃって sorry でもでもずっとずっと secret
Sorry if I troubled you, but let's keep it a secret forever and ever.
して なんて いらない 決まり です
It's not that we don't have to do it, it's a decision!
驚かさちゃうほど 大きい声で pretty fever !
With a voice so loud it startles—pretty fever!
予想上回って裏切っちゃって… 覚悟はいいですか ？
Surpassing expectations and betraying them... are you ready for this?
i like me 絶対譲れないから
"I like me"—I will never give in!
いつだってそう「僕なんて」さって
Always saying, "Someone like me..."
俯いてばかりのMayday
With nothing but downcast Maydays.
つまづいて泣いて 「どうせ」って口癖が染みついてさ
Stumbling and crying, "So what?" became a habit.
いつからかまた積もる焦燥
Impatience keeps piling up since when.
でも胸の奥にある光
But the light deep in my heart
繋ぐ点と線の上
On the line connecting dots and lines
踏み出すイメージの先へ
Beyond the image of taking a step forward,
遠くだっていい まず 虹をまたいで
Even if it's far, first stride across the rainbow.
さあ 心のままに音を奏でる
Now, play the music as your heart desires.
逸る鼓動は今を刻む証だ
A racing heartbeat is proof of marking the present.
響け 僕らの想いを乗せて
Resound, carrying our feelings,
高く遠く 歌を紡いで
Spinning songs high and far.
新しいフェーズにみんなを連れてくよ
I'll take everyone to a new phase.
自信を自足する呪いが必要なんです
I need a spell to self-supplement confidence.
I want to チェンジ本気でいっちゃったから Yeah
I want to change because I went for it seriously, yeah.
いつでもセッションを I got feel Yeah
Always sessioning, I got feel, yeah.
奏でるよ Pretty fever
Playing it, Pretty fever.
みんなお疲れ様！
Good work, everyone!
頑張って！いってらっしゃい！
Do your best! Have fun!
ねえ、聞こえてる？
Hey, can you hear me?
きみと共にギリギリなファイト
A desperate fight on the edge with you.
あかさたにミゼラブルなファイト
A miserable fight, starting from scratch.
ラブはいつもアナキズムなファイト
Love is always an anarchist fight.
わたしだけのインモラルなファイト
An immoral fight that is mine alone.
さよなら 言えない
I can't say goodbye.
わたしは ダメだな
I'm no good.
わからない
I don't know.
自分が わからない
I don't even know myself.
この気持ち 消えそうもない こんなにも なくならない
This feeling won't fade, it won't disappear at all.
いけないんだと思えば思うほど 加速するの
The more I think I shouldn't, the more it accelerates.
もう 自分自身 が 怖い けど
I'm already scared of myself, but...
今 信じてみるよ
I'll try believing in it now.
何を 失っても
No matter what I lose.
きみの御許に と決めたの
I've decided to be by your side.
たとえ 明日になれば
Even if tomorrow comes...
消えゆく 運命でも
Even in a fate destined to vanish.
わたしを止める
To stop me...
理由にもならないよ
It's not even a reason.
わたし きみの前なら インモラリストだよ
In front of you, I am an immoralist.
きみと共にギリギリなファイト
A desperate fight on the edge with you.
あかさたにミゼラブルなファイト
A miserable fight, starting from scratch.
ラブはいつもアナキズムなファイト
Love is always an anarchist fight.
わたしだけのインモラルなファイト
An immoral fight that is mine alone.
悲しみ 苦しみ 憎しみ おいでよ
Sadness, suffering, hatred, come on over.
わたしは いつでも 迎える 覚悟さ
I'm always ready to welcome them.
そんなふうに思えるようにもなったの
I've come to be able to feel that way.
不思議だな 出会ってくれて わたし少し強くなれた
It's strange. Meeting you made me a bit stronger.
涙なんて神様にあげるから だから お願い 自由をください
I'll give my tears to God, so please, give me freedom.
どこにでもゆける翼を
Wings that can go anywhere.
たとえかなうはずもない
Even if it's bound to never come true.
何かに襲われても
Even if attacked by something.
今のわたしなら 一歩だって引かないよ
The me I am now won't back down even a step.
わたしきみの前なら ヒロイックだよ
In front of you, I am heroic.
ただ ただ 愛したいのに
Even though I just want to love...
ただ ただ 苦しくて
It's just so painful...
届け 届け 届いて きみのこころに
Reach, reach, reach into your heart.
このわたしのインモラル 一人で抱えるには少し 重すぎるの
This immorality of mine is a bit too heavy to carry alone.
もういっそのこと 全て捨ててしまおうなんて 呟いて眠るけれど
Murmuring that I should just throw everything away as I fall asleep,
いつもきみの夢ばかり
I always dream only of you.
ねえ 聞こえてる?
Hey, can you hear me?
きみと共にギリギリなファイト
A close-call fight with you,
あからさまにミゼラブルなファイト
An obviously miserable fight,
わたしだけのインモラルなファイト
An immoral fight meant only for me.
さよなら 言えない
I can't say goodbye,
わたしは ダメだな
I'm so hopeless, aren't I?
わからない わからない 自分が わからない
I don't know, I don't know, I don't understand myself.
この気持ち 消えそうもない
This feeling won't even vanish...
答え なんて 出なくても
Even if answers don't come out,
立ち向かうよ
I will stand and face it.
導き出した答え
The answer I found by meeting you,
止まらない 止まれない
I won't stop, I won't stop,
きみの御許にとめたの
I decided to go to your side.
きみのため 今戦うの
I'm fighting for you now.
だいすき
I love you,
あいしてる
I want to be with you forever.
たとえ明日になれば
Even if tomorrow comes,
消えゆく運命でも
Even if it's a fading destiny,
わたしを止める
You stop me,
理由にもならないよ
It's not even a reason.
わたし きみの前なら インモラリストだよ
In front of you, I'm an immoralist.
ねえ 聞こえてる?
Hey, can you hear me?
きみと共にギリギリなファイト
A close-call fight with you,
あからさまにミゼラブルなファイト
An obviously miserable fight,
ラヴはいつもアンチカズムなファイト
Love is always an anarchist fight.
わたしだけのインモラルなファイト
An immoral fight meant only for me.
淡々 言葉を吐いた
Threw words like we don't even care,
あんな思い出に泣いたのは
Cried over memories we share.
今日で終わりにしないか
Can we make this the end so I can leave it there?
1,2の合図を待って
1, 2, and I'm ready to go.
ユーエミー 手を取り合ったのは
You and me, hands that we both hold.
僕の勇気ある行動 フェイス
In the days I was going through a very bold phase.
立ち止まんないでいいんだからね
Tell me if you wanna keep it on, just say.
空々しいな この人生
What a fickle thing, the life I lead today.
できないだなんて言わないでね
"Can't do it at all" don't say it in that way.
今更なんて言わないでね
I don't wanna hear that "No, it's way too late."
僕ら今さあさあ輪になって回り始める
And now we're going round round running on end,
段々嫌になって
Spinning my heart into the ground.
でも好きになる
Hating you then falling for you again.
ねえねえわかんないや
And why why oh who am i?
自分会議も
Don't get myself at all.
どんどん中に寄って
And try try to reach that line,
でも離れてく
But never reach in time.
ぱっぱっ音に乗って踊り始める
And pound pound into a sick rave,
散々嫌になって
Dancing my heart into the ground.
でも好きになる
Hating this game then loving you the same.
ねえねえわかんないや
And why why oh what am i?
この先もずっと 僕の心をシェイクシェイクイェイ
My heart is awake and going shake shake yeah.
大正解なんてないのさ
If there's no right or a wrong way,
じゃあ一体どこに向かえば
Then what's my goal or the end game?
物語は終わりますか
Are we now facing down our story's last page?
1,2の合図を待って
1, 2, and I'm ready to go.
ユーエミ手と触れ合ったのは
You and me touch fingers slow.
僕の勇気ある行動 フェイス
In the days I was going through a very bold phase.
囚まったって意味ないんだって
Talking like a rock as if you comprehend.
恥ずかしがった夢にばいばいです
Every awkward dream I'm leaving, bye bye then.
この先ずっとよろしくね よろしくね
Now I'm in your hands so good luck with the rest.
君と今さあさあ交わって目を逸らじあう
And now it's you and me meeting again,
段々嫌になって
You look away although I keep...
でも好きになる
Hating this then falling for you again.
ねえねえわかんないや
And why why oh who am i?
自分会議も
Don't get myself at all.
どんどん様になって
And try try and almost find,
崩れ落ちてく
But fall apart each time.
ぱっぱっ触れる前に消えてしまうの
And pop pop into the night air,
散々嫌になって
You disappear before I stop.
でも好きになる
Stop hating this game and loving you the same.
ねえねえわかんないや
And why why oh what am i?
この先もずっとわかりあえるまで僕たちは
What do I do? I wanna try.
今更なんて言わないでね
I don't wanna hear that "No, it's way too late."
僕ら今さあさあ輪になって回り始める
And now we're going round round running on end.
淡々 言葉を吐いた
Threw words like we don't even care
あんな思い出に泣いたのは
Cried over memories we share
今日で終わりにしないか
Can we make this the end?
ねえねえ わかんないや
Hey hey, I don't get it
自分会議も
Even my internal debates
どんどん中に寄って でも離れてく
Closing in tighter, yet drifting apart
ぱっぱっ 音に乗って 踊り始める
Pop pop, riding the beat and starting to dance
散々嫌になって
Hating it all so much
でも好きになる
But falling for you again
ねえねえ わかんないや
Hey hey, I don't get it
この先もずっと
And from here on out
僕の心をシェイクシェイク yeah
Shake, shake my heart, yeah!
目が覚めたなら
When I woke up
君が笑って
Thinking you would laugh
そんな世界が続くと思ってた
And that world would continue
当たり前には少し足りない
Slightly lacking from the ordinary
歪んだ視界から見てた
Viewed from a distorted field of view
青い夜 何度目の朝で
On the blue night, after how many mornings
打ち明けた恋のように
Like a confessed love
少し酸っぱいままで
Still a bit sour
出掛けたら 近付いてく
When I set out, getting closer
ぼくらデリケート 淡い夢を見せてあげよう
We are delicate, let me show you a tender dream
たまにはいいことあるかも
Sometimes good things might happen
ご褒美にはチョコレート 甘い夢を見れたなら
Chocolate as a reward, if you could see a sweet dream
それがすべてだなんて笑ってみよう
Let's laugh as if that's everything
曖昧だって大体だって続く気がして
Feeling like it'll continue, vague and general as it is
夜空を見上げた なんとなくから見えた景色が
I looked up at the night sky, and the scenery seen from somehow
新しい世界へほらね 導くよ
Will guide you to a new world, look
回り続けるこの星はだれのもの?
Whose world is this that keeps spinning?
難しいハナシなら食後にして
If it's a difficult talk, let's leave it after meals
近付いてく ぼくらデリケート
Getting closer, we are delicate
淡い夢を見せてあげよう
Let me show you a tender dream
たまにはいいことあるかも
Sometimes good things might happen
ご褒美にはチョコレート
Chocolate as a reward
甘い夢を見れたなら それがすべてだなんて
If you could see a sweet dream, as if that's everything
笑い飛ばそう あの丘まで進め
Let's laugh it away, go straight to that hill
ストレート 見えない音に耳傾け 聴こえた?
Listen straight to the invisible sound, did you hear?
手招きする声 いくつかのバリケード壊せ
A beckoning voice, break down several barricades
知れば知るほどわからなくもなるくらい不思議な世界
A world so mysterious that the more you know, the less you understand
近付いてく ぼくらデリケート
Getting closer, we are delicate
淡い夢を見せてあげよう
Let me show you a tender dream
たまにはいいことあるかも
Sometimes good things might happen
ご褒美にはチョコレート
Chocolate as a reward
甘い夢を見れたなら それがすべてだなんて
If you could see a sweet dream, as if that's everything
笑って見せよう あの丘まで進め
Let's show a smile, go straight to that hill
ストレート 見えない音に耳傾け 聴こえた?
Listen straight to the invisible sound, did you hear?
手招きする声 いくつかのバリケード
A beckoning voice, break down several barricades
壊せ 知れば知るほどわからなくもなる
Break it down, a world so mysterious
くらい不思議な世界
That the more you know, the less you understand
turn it up to the funky beat,
that's for you & me.
騒ぎ立てろビート
Rouse the beat,
it's only for you & me.
瞳にキラキラワンダーランド
Sparkling wonderland in our eyes,
夜空にキスしたバタフライ
A butterfly kissing the night sky.
おいでよエンジェル一緒にムーンライト
Chase the engine together with moonlight,
恋をデコレーション
Decorate our love.
まるでストロベリー甘いクリームの上にお気に入りのハッピー飾ろう
Like strawberry jam on sweet cream,
いくつもの鍵でキミと扉を開ける
Opening the door with countless keys,
星のジュエリー降り注ぐ shining my dream
Jewels of stars falling into shining my dream.
出会って「ふたり」になる you & me
Meeting you makes us "two", you & me.
昨日じゃないってそれだけで good morning!
Not yesterday, that alone is good morning.
“ハジマリ”でしょ?
"Is it the beginning?"
出会って未来になる you & me
Meeting you shapes our future, you & me.
愛よりもっとloveな笑顔で
With an ever-loving smile,
終わんない happy dance
An endless happy dance.
つないだドキドキ time
Connecting tightly, thrilling time.
魔法のケーキどんなに食べても全然減らない ah
No matter how much magical cake we eat, it never runs out.
見つめたその両目の中はヤバい キラめく星の数がハンパない
The stars in those eyes are immeasurable.
虹色シューズで時間旅行
Time travel in rainbow shoes.
いたずら小悪魔はベビーフェイス
Mischievous imp, a baby face.
なんでもレッスン冒険の気分
Any lesson is a thrilling adventure.
指先にキラリネイルのブルーで
Blue nail polish sparkling on fingertips.
パラダイス空のカケラを閉じ込めたいな
Want to capture fragments of paradise in the sky.
見つめあうたびにおもちゃ箱を逃だす
Escaping the toy box every time we lock eyes.
恋のメロディーつかまえて! growing my dream
Catching the melody of love, growing my dream.
出会って「ふたり」になる you & me
Meeting you makes us "two", you & me.
キミがいるってそれだけで sunny day! rainy day!
Just having you there is a sunny day, rainy day.
“トクベツ”なのは
That's our "special secret".
出会って言葉になる you & me
Meeting you gives words to our feelings, you & me.
highよりもっとfullなボリュームで
With an even fuller volume than high,
伝えたい baby love
I want to convey this baby love.
1. 2. 3. 4. now, ready to the motto atsui stage he
1, 2, 3, 4, now, ready to the hotter stage.
ゲームはファンタジーだらけスタートからゴールまで
Games are just fantasy, from start to goal.
愛のファンファーレを鳴らし
Ring the love's fanfare.
どんなハチャメチャな夢でもこうやって真剣に一心不乱に願い続けていれば
Even in the wildest dream, wish earnestly with all your heart.
リアルになるいつかはそんじゃなければ全部ビッグバン
It will become real before you know it, everything goes big bang.
出会って「ふたり」になる you & me
Meeting you makes us "two", you & me.
昨日じゃないってそれだけで good morning!
Not yesterday, that alone is good morning.
“ハジマリ”でしょ?
"Is it the beginning?"
出会って未来になる you & me
Meeting you shapes our future, you & me.
愛よりもっとloveな笑顔で
With an ever-loving smile,
終わんない happy dance
An endless happy dance.
つないだドキドキ time
Connecting tightly, thrilling time.
魔法のケーキどんなに食べても全然減らない ah
No matter how much magical cake we eat, it never runs out.
見つめたその両目の中はヤバい キラめく星の数がハンパない
The stars in those eyes are immeasurable.
虹色シューズで時間旅行
Time travel in rainbow shoes.
いたずら小悪魔はベビーフェイス
Mischievous imp, a baby face.
なんでもレッスン冒険の気分
Any lesson is a thrilling adventure.
指先にキラリネイルのブルーで
Blue nail polish sparkling on fingertips.
パラダイス空のカケラを閉じ込めたいな
Want to capture fragments of paradise in the sky.
見つめあうたびにおもちゃ箱を逃だす
Escaping the toy box every time we lock eyes.
恋のメロディーつかまえて! growing my dream
Catching the melody of love, growing my dream.
出会って「ふたり」になる you & me
Meeting you makes us "two", you & me.
キミがいるってそれだけで sunny day! rainy day!
Just having you there is a sunny day, rainy day.
“トクベツ”なのは
That's our "special secret".
出会って言葉になる you & me
Meeting you gives words to our feelings, you & me.
highよりもっとfullなボリュームで
With an even fuller volume than high,
伝えたい baby love
I want to convey this baby love.
turn it up to the funky beat,
that's for you & me.
騒ぎ立てろビート
Rouse the beat,
it's only for you & me.
bring it back yo, rock 'en roll!!!
Bring it back, rock 'n' roll!
life goes on 満足してた 少しの希望だけで
Life went on, satisfied with just a little hope.
待ってれば 誰かが未来決めてくれていた
If you wait, someone would always decide the future for you.
なんて小さい自分なんだろう? bust it up!
How small am I? Bust it up!
move it up and break it!
今すぐ夢まで走ろう
Let's run to our dreams right now.
gamble, you gatta chance to make a rumble!
Gamble, you gotta chance to make a rumble!
ギリギリのステージ
A razor-thin stage.
gamble, you gatta dive in to a scramble!
Gamble, you gotta dive in to a scramble!
一ミリも迷わず
Without hesitating even a millimeter.
守るべきモノなんて 実はそんなに無い
The things we should protect aren't really there at all.
少しだけ強がって 賭けましょう全部 play the game!
Play the game with a little courage!
今すぐ夢まで走ろう
Let's run straight to our dreams right now!
bring back yo it's the right time,hey boy,rock'n roll
bring back yo, it's the right time, hey boy, rock'n roll
Gamble, you gatta chance to make a Rumble!
Gamble, you gotta chance to make a Rumble!
ギリギリのステージ oh yeah!
On the edge of the stage, oh yeah!
Gamble, you gatta dive in to a scramble!
Gamble, you gotta dive into a scramble!
一ミリも迷わず check it out come on!
Without hesitating even a millimeter, check it out come on!
守るべきモノなんて 実はそんなに無い
Things we need to protect are actually so few.
少しだけ強がって 賭けましょう全部 play the game!
Get a little tougher and let's bet everything, play the game!
let's gamble hey jumbo now shake your bum and do the rumble
鋭いラインを三本 テンション上がりきりでボンボー 登場move三人衆 皆様の安眠中 爆音で『お前らウザい!』と言われても延々と
Sharpening three lines, tension through the roof with bumbou, three people taking the stage while everyone sleeps, blast music saying "you're annoying!" but dragging it out anyway...
i like to move it move it i'll make you move into it
国産のエグいノイズかます ギラギラ欲望さらす スタートからゴールまでまとめてワープして マッハ55で抜け出していこう to your next stage
Spitting out domestic edgy noise, shining desires, warp straight from start to goal, let's smash through at Mach 55 to your next stage!
boy can't you see?
自分らしさ 削って過ごしていた
I've been spending my days cutting away my true self,
代償に手に入れたのは 古くさいモラル
and what I got in return was an outdated morality.
just got to get yo back and bring it back on
怯懦な この群れから 今 bust it up!
From this cowardly flock, now bust it up!
here we go, back to move it up and break it!
何も持たないで 飛び出そう
Let's leap out without holding onto anything!
bring back yo it's the right time,hey boy,rock'n roll
bring back yo, it's the right time, hey boy, rock'n roll
Gamble, you gatta chance to make a Rumble!
Gamble, you gotta chance to make a Rumble!
研ぎ澄ませていく oh yeah!
Let's polish it up and make it shine, oh yeah!
Gamble, you gatta dive in to a scramble!
Gamble, you gotta dive into a scramble!
直感を信じて check it out come on!
Trusting your intuition, check it out come on!
本命の 君の愛 以外は要らなくて
We don't need anything other than your true love.
少しでも迷うもの 捨てましょう it's gonna feel so fine!
Let's throw away whatever makes us hesitate, it's gonna feel so fine!
breakdown
come on hey do the rumble
152! ムラムラとbeatが挑戦する モツ MC 超 ティーン エイジャー 人類 最速 rap 芸術 speakeasy へ ようこそ 大盤振舞う 緋花
152! Muramura to beat ga chousen suru, motsu MC chou teen eijah, jinrui sosoku rap geisha, speakeasy he youkoso daihan furumau hibana...
全部 張っ て スッ ちゃう か ? ハ ! gamble rumble
zenbu hatte sutchau ka? ha! gamble rumble
Gamble, you gatta chance to make a Rumble!
Gamble, you gotta chance to make a Rumble!
溢れ出す眩しさが
Overflowing, dazzling brilliance...
Gamble, you gatta dive in to a scramble!
Gamble, you gotta dive into a scramble!
はじまりそうな last game
It's about to begin, that last game!
Gamble, you gatta chance to make a Rumble!
Gamble, you gotta chance to make a Rumble!
ギリギリのステージ oh yeah!
On the edge of the stage, oh yeah!
Gamble, you gatta dive in to a scramble!
Gamble, you gotta dive into a scramble!
一ミリも迷わず check it out come on!
Without hesitating even a millimeter, check it out come on!
一瞬の選択で すべてを失くしても
Even if a split-second choice makes you lose everything,
後悔は見せないで 明るく負けて泣きましょ
don't show any regret, lose cheerfully and cry!
bring back hey,one more time! bring back yo it's the right time,hey boy,rock'n roll
bring back hey, one more time! bring back yo, it's the right time, hey boy, rock'n roll
Gamble, you gatta chance to make a Rumble!
Gamble, you gotta chance to make a Rumble!
ez do dance
i can hear my voice 今 始まる
i can hear my voice, starting right now
midnight time から この 場所 で
midnight time, from this place,
行くあてが同じ仲間と 全ての嘘脱ぎさる
walking with companions who share the same destination, shedding all our lies.
何もなくて道もなくて 踊る君はどこから
With nothing and no path to follow, where are you dancing from?
逃げて行くのさ 去って行くの不思議なほど眩しい
Are you running away? Are you leaving? So dazzlingly strange,
ささやく夢語り合って 傷なめ合ってる堕天使
whispering dreams to each other, healing each other's wounds like fallen angels.
easy go easy go 笑顔だけ ひとときの輪をつなぐよ
easy go easy go, with just a smile, connecting a fleeting circle.
i 've got feeling
i've got a feeling
突き抜けてく
Breaking through,
街が目覚める頃
as the town awakens,
朝焼けにくちづけてる
kissing the morning glow,
波も抱きしめてる
and embracing the waves too.
Ez Do Dance Ez Do Dance
踊る君を見てる…
watching you dance...
Ez Do Dance Ez Do Dance
君だけを見ている
looking only at you...
欲しいものはいつでも
Whatever I want, whenever,
不意に出会う偶然
an unexpected coincidence strikes.
見えない明日 突然に
An unseen tomorrow, suddenly,
めぐりあえるときめき
a thrilling encounter awaits.
午前5時 永遠のルール
5:00 AM, the eternal rule
変わる瞬間
in the moment it changes.
きっと きっと 愛なんて
Surely, surely, not that we can
呼べるものじゃないけど
call it love, but still,
I've got feeling 突き抜けてく
I've got feeling, breaking through,
街が目、覚める頃
as the town awakens,
朝焼けにくちづけてる
kissing the morning glow,
波も抱きしめてる
and embracing the waves too.
Ez Do Dance Ez Do Dance
踊る君を見てる…
watching you dance...
Ez Do Dance Ez Do Dance
君だけを見ている
looking only at you...
I've got feeling 突き抜けてく
I've got feeling, breaking through,
街が目、覚める頃
as the town awakens,
朝焼けにくちづけてる
kissing the morning glow,
波も抱きしめてる
and embracing the waves too.
Ez Do Dance Ez Do Dance
踊る君を見てる…
watching you dance...
Ez Do Dance Ez Do Dance
君だけを見ている
looking only at you...
I've got feeling 突き抜けてく
I've got feeling, breaking through,
街が目、覚める頃
as the town awakens,
朝焼けにくちづけてる
kissing the morning glow,
てっぺんとろうぜ!
Let's reach the very top!
おねだりしてみてほしいの
I want you to try begging me,
お願いダーリン!
Please, Darling!
言いたいことは言わないし
You don't say what you want to say,
やりたい方からやりたいことまで
and decide everything your own way.
ねえそんなの馬鹿みたいじゃない?
Hey, isn't that just ridiculous?
いつも思わせぶりな感じで
Always acting so suggestive,
察してほしい感じで
expecting me to read between the lines.
わざと口にしないのズルくない?
Isn't it sly how you keep quiet?
バカじゃないの?
Are you an idiot?
お願いダーリン 見て聞いて
Please, Darling, look and listen,
欲しいのは形のないもの
what I want is something intangible.
バカにしないでよ 見て聞いて
Don't make a fool of me, look and listen,
覗いてよ 瞳の奥の方
peek deep into the depths of my eyes.
まっすぐ見つめて おねだりしてみて
Look straight at me and try begging,
ダーリン 私の気持ちを全然知らないわ
Darling, you don't know my feelings at all.
あるほど健気に見せつけてきたのに
Even though I've acted so devoted,
今ではすっかり知らんぷり?
now you're acting totally clueless?
ていうかそれって胡坐かいてるだけなんじゃないですか
Or rather, aren't you taking it for granted?
つれないときはつれないし
When you're cold, you're cold,
そっちが中々言い出さないからいつも私が舵取りじゃん?
and since you never speak up, I always steer!
ねえなんだかバカみたいじゃない? そうじゃない?
Hey, isn't that kind of foolish?
どこか足元見てる感じで
Somewhere, it feels like you're taking advantage,
値踏みされてる感じで
like I'm being weighed and priced.
駆け引きやら勝ち負けじゃなくない?
Isn't this more than just winning or losing?
そうゆうめんどくさいことしてるからめんどくさいこと
Playing games like this just causes trouble.
どうなるんだよ?
...how does that happen?
お願いダーリン ねえ聞いて
Please, darling, listen to me.
切なさは飾りじゃないのよ
Pathos isn't just decoration.
よそ見しないで 逃げないで
Don't look away, don't run away.
触ってよ 心の奥の方
Touch me deep inside my heart.
一瞬のことじゃない
It's not just a momentary thing.
おねだりしてはくれないの?
Won't you pester me just a little?
言葉にできない臆病さは
Cowardice you can't put into words...
したたかさではないのよ
Isn't about being strong.
甘えてないで 口に出してよ
Don't be spoiled, say it to my face.
ちゃんとこっち向いてたら!
Turn this way properly!
お願いダーリン 見て聞いて
Please, darling, look at me and listen.
欲しいのは 形のないもの
What I want is something shapeless.
馬鹿にしないで 見て聞いて
Don't make fun of me, look at me, listen.
覗いてよ 瞳の奥の方
Peer deep into my eyes.
寡黙なダーリン 寝てないで
Silent darling, don't just sleep.
暴いてよ 私の素顔を
Expose my honest face!
お願いダーリン そばにいて
Please, darling, stay by my side.
触らせて 心の奥の方
Let me touch deep in your heart.
真っ直ぐ見つめて
Gaze straight at me...
おねだりしてみて欲しいの?
Won't you pester me?
お願いダーリン かわいい!
Please, darling... so cute!
せーのっ! いにさんはいっ!
Ready, 1, 2, 3, go!
これよりご覧いただきますのは
What we present to you now...
カブキ者たちの栄枯盛衰
is the rise and fall of the kabuki performers.
時代は常に日進月歩
Times are constantly changing at a rapid pace,
聞いてってよ老若男女
listen up, young and old alike!
一見は勧善懲悪
At first glance, punishing evil and rewarding good,
悪者どもを一刀両断
cutting down villains in one stroke.
「でもホントにそれだけで楽しいの?」
"But is it really fun with just that?"
もうなんだってこんにゃく問答
It's all just a confusing debate now.
どこからともなく現れて
Appearing out of nowhere,
すぐどこか行っちゃって神出鬼没
and disappearing just as quickly like a phantom.
チャンスを待ったら一日千秋
Waiting for a chance feels like a thousand years,
追いかければ東奔西走
chasing after them means running all over.
時代は常に千変万化
Times are always changing in a thousand ways,
人の心は複雑怪奇
and human hearts are complex and bizarre.
「でも本気でそんなこと言ってんの?」
"Do you really mean what you say?"
もうどうにも満身創痍
I'm completely exhausted.
めぐりめぐって夜の町
Wandering around the night town,
キミは合図出し踊りだす
you give the signal and start to dance!
華麗に花弁 散らすように
Spinning around like scattering flower petals,
髪も振り乱して
tossing your hair about!
一昨日、昨日、今日と、明日と、明後日と
The day before yesterday, yesterday, today, tomorrow, and the day after,
この宴は続く
this banquet goes on.
踊れ、歌エ、一心不乱に回レ!
Dance, sing, and spin with single-minded devotion!
今宵は雪月花
Tonight is Setsugetsuka!
この世に平安訪れるの?
Will peace ever visit this world?
のべつ幕無し丁丁発止
Without lowering the curtain, with a bold start,
兵ども千客万来 ひしめき合う群雄割拠
warlords gather from near and far,
伸るか反るか一攫千金 気付いたら絶対絶命
win or lose, it's a make-or-break moment,
「でも本音のとこ、どうなってんの?」
"But what is really on your mind?"
もうまったく奇想天外
It's totally out of this world.
たどりたどりて夜の町
Tracing our way through the night town,
迷い一つなく踊りだす
we start dancing without a single hesitation.
華麗に花弁 散らすように
Spinning around like scattering flower petals,
髪も振り乱して
tossing your hair about!
一昨日、昨日、今日と、明日と、明後日と
The day before yesterday, yesterday, today, tomorrow, and the day after,
この宴は続く
this banquet goes on.
踊れ、歌エ、一心不乱に回レ!
Dance, sing, and spin with single-minded devotion!
今宵は雪月花
Tonight is Setsugetsuka!
花で一つ、鳥で二つ
One for flowers, two for birds,
手打ち鳴らす
clap your hands to the rhythm.
風で三つ、鳴呼、月出て四つ
Three for the wind, four when the moon rises,
鳴らす鳴らす……
make it resound, make it resound...
花で一つ、鳥で二つ
One for flowers, two for birds,
手打ち鳴らす
clap your hands to the rhythm.
風で三つ、鳴呼、月出て四つ
Three for the wind, four when the moon rises,
鳴らす鳴らす……
make it resound, make it resound...
華麗に花弁 散らすように
Spinning around like scattering flower petals,
髪も振り乱して
tossing your hair about!
一昨日、昨日、今日と、明日と、明後日と
The day before yesterday, yesterday, today, tomorrow, and the day after,
この宴は続く
this banquet goes on.
This banquet continues,
踊れ歌え 一心不乱に回れ！
dance and sing, spin with all your heart!
今宵は何曜日か？
What day of the week is tonight?
水木金？
Wed, Thu, Fri?
土日月火？
Sat, Sun, Mon, Tue?
はっはっはっはっ
Ha-ha-ha-ha!
ぽんっ！
Pon!
ウェルカム！今日はポルカのプロデュースライブ、
Welcome! Today is Polka's produced live,
そしてポルカの誕生日ライブにお越しいただき本当に本当にありがとうございます！
and thank you so much for coming to Polka's birthday live!
たくさんの仲間たちが来てくれてすごーく嬉しいです！
I'm super happy that so many friends came to join!
すごいぞ なんかちょっと… それでもみんなが横にいるからポルカは頑張って歌いまっす！
It's amazing... wait, even so, everyone is by my side so Polka will do her best to sing!
ありがとうございます！そしてまた次の誕生日、これからもよろしくね！
Thank you! And for the next birthday, please keep supporting me!
準備はできてますか？いくぜ！
Are you ready? Let's go!
さぁさぁ近くにおいで、きっと誰もが仰天
Come closer, everyone will surely be amazed
奇想天外なショーの始まりさ！
at the beginning of this outlandish show!
ぐっと光るでしょ？
It shines brightly, right?
おっと幼いって？
Whoa, too childish?
それでは準備OKですか？
Are you ready for this?
愉快な動物たち、玉乗りピエロ
Cheerful animals, ball-balancing clowns,
ハラハラドキドキしちゃうでしょ！
it makes your heart race, doesn't it!
真っ赤な輪くぐらせ、綱渡りして
Jumping through bright red hoops, walking the tightrope,
ちょっとくらいのドジなんて愛嬌よ
a little bit of clumsiness is just charming!
Come on! Light up!
とっておきのライブもっとしてないで
Don't just keep our special live to yourself,
もっとさもっと手を叩こう！
let's clap even more!
ほらほら空いておいで、でも回るような
Come on over, even in this spinning world,
逆さきっとここだけだよ
it's upside down, right here only!
ホログラムみたい、キラキラ奇跡が踊る
Like a hologram, sparkling miracles dance,
いつかは世界中を、虜にしちゃうぞ！
someday we'll captivate the whole world!
うーん明日の演目はどうしようかな
Hmm, what should tomorrow's act be?
屋根裏で秘密の作戦会議さ
A secret strategy meeting in the attic.
いっぱいの観客席が、あっと驚くようなとびきりのショーを見せましょう
Let's show them a dazzling performance that will astound the packed audience!
思い付いたらジッとしてられない
When inspiration strikes we can't stay still,
座員を引き連れて Lets go!
leading the troupe, let's go!
ねぇあれがやりたい、これもやりたい！
Hey, I want to do that, I want to do this too!
どうして時間って足りないの？
Why is there never enough time?
みんな、最後まで盛り上がっていけー！
Everyone, keep the hype going till the end!
いくぜ！
Let's go!
手拍子お願いいします！
Please give us a round of applause!
ペンライト振ってる人はもっともっと振って、みんなの色を振っちゃって！
Everyone with penlights, wave them even more, let's paint the venue with your colors!
最後行きます！
Final stretch!
上手くいなくって
Even when things don't go well,
空回りばかりで
and I just spin my wheels in place,
少し落ち込んじゃう日もあるけれど
and there are days when I feel down,
見ててね 大丈夫！いつでも
please watch over me! It's okay! No matter what,
クヨクヨしてらんないし
I won't mope around,
顔を上げて 今日のステージがほら
lift your head up—look, today's stage
ねぇ待ってるのさ
is waiting for you!
強く強く願うんだ どんな夢だって
Wish strongly and firmly, no matter what dream it is,
そうきっと叶うはず
yes, it's sure to come true.
何も怖くない ポルカの声は全部ちゃんと届いてるよ
There's nothing to be afraid of. Polka's voice is reaching everyone loud and clear!
さぁ新しい次元 新しい舞台へ もっとさもっと突き進もう！
Now, onto a new dimension, a new stage, let's push forward even more!
まだまだ付いておいで 笑い転げちゃうサーカス 絶対ここだけだよ
Keep following us! A circus that will make you laugh until you roll, right here only!
初めての仲間 景色に心も踊る
Our first friends, our hearts dance to the scenery,
今にも世界中を 虜にしちゃうから
because we're about to captivate the whole world right now!
目を離しちゃダメだぞ
Don't take your eyes off me!
本当にありがとうございました！！
Thank you so very much!!
そして、結果発表のときがやってきた……
And now, the moment of the results has arrived...
優勝は……
The winner is...
尾丸ポルカ率いる「ホローバックプロデュース」です おめでとうございます！！
Omaru Polka's "Hollow Back Produce"! Congratulations!!
え…？私達が…優勝……？
Eh...? We... won...?
私達が…？
Us...?
え…あ…えっ…？
Eh... ah... what...?
嬉しいっ…！！
I'm so happy...!!
ありがとう…ありがとうみんな！！
Thank you... thank you everyone!!
ここまで来られたのも本当にみんなのおかげです
Making it this far is truly thanks to all of you.
ありがとうございました！！！！ これからもよろしくお願いしますっ！！
Thank you so much!!!! We look forward to your continued support!!
えっ？ご褒美に宣伝させていただいてもいいですか？わーい！！
Huh? Can I promote my merchandise as a reward? Yay!!
というわけで尾丸ポルカ誕生日記念2022のグッズが販売開始されます！
And with that, Omaru Polka's 2022 Birthday Commemoration goods go on sale!
こちら誕生日記念フルセットは、なんと記念グッズ3種類、記念ボイス1種類に、尾丸ポルカ直筆サイン入り！
This Birthday Commemoration Full Set includes 3 kinds of goods, 1 voice pack, and an autographed card by Omaru Polka!
きな子先生描き下ろしチェキ風ブロマイドカードがついてくる！カードってめっちゃテンション上がるよな！
It comes with a cheki-style bromide card illustrated by Kinako-sensei! Cards always get you super hyped, right?
こちら、そのほか単品販売もございます。なんとラバーマット、こちら3,000円はきな子先生描き下ろし！
Individual items are also available! The rubber mat is 3,000 yen, illustrated by Kinako-sensei!
めちゃくちゃ可愛いですよね！これ、あのね、ほんとにね、オマ、なんだろね、ポルカ
It's insanely cute! This, you know, really, Omaru... what is it, Polka...
「お前だけの尾丸ポルカだよ」っていうところをイメージしております。どうでしょうか？ポルカあなたに、あなたにだけしか見せない尾丸ポルカ可愛いでしょう？ふふふふ。というわけで
is imaging the feeling of "I'm Omaru Polka, just for you." What do you think? Cute, right, showing only you? Hehehe. So,
こちらさらに！全世界お揃い宣言！隠れポルカ推しリュック、こちら7,000円になります！
and furthermore! The worldwide matching declaration: Secret Polka Fan Backpack, priced at 7,000 yen!
はあ、もうこれね、現地で使いたい！絶対使いたい！なんならポルカもこのラバーマットのところで一緒に背負ってるからお揃いなんだよ！
Ah, I definitely want to use this at live venues! I totally want to use it! Polka even carries it with this rubber mat design, so we match!
ポルカとお揃いな上にさらにこれを付けて……全員お揃いなので、全世界お揃いになりますね！
Matching with Polka, plus wearing this... everyone matches, making it a worldwide match!
ということで、もしね、あの現地に行く機会などお外を歩く機会があれば、ま、これをね、しょっちゃって、というわけで、ま、普段使いもめちゃくちゃできるんだよね、これ。
So if you have the chance to go to a live venue or walk outside, you can just wear this, and you know, it's actually super practical for everyday use.
ざいんくんの、これね、チャームがついてる上で、えー、裏地がね、なんとあららららららこれね、尾丸ポルカからの良い仕事してくれますねえ！
It has the Zain-kun charm, and the lining—oh my goodness—Omaru Polka really does good work here!
マジでちょうどいいサイズ感です。学生さんも社会人のお休みにめちゃくちゃ合います。
It's seriously the perfect size. It's great for students and working adults on their days off.
そしてそして、こちら大注目のグッズ、えー、うちでも外でも回らないポルペラヘアバンド！こちら2,500円になっております！
And next up, this highly anticipated item: the Non-Spinning Polpera Hair Band for home or outside! This is 2,500 yen!
あー、いるよね！これもう付けちゃってさ、これ付けて原宿歩きたいけど、あの楽しそうよね、そうなったら。え、お前もポルペラ付いてるの？ってなりそうですよね。
Ah, you gotta have this! Wearing this to walk in Harajuku would be fun. People would be like, "Wait, you have a Polpera too?"
ま、普段使いとしては、ま、簡単に顔を洗うときの前髪をかきあげるのが無難かなと思うんですが、
Well, for everyday use, sweeping back your bangs while washing your face is probably the safest bet, but
なんだろう、ポルカよくスタジオとかでこういうのつけてる人を見るんで、多分なんかあの、使ってる人もこういうのつけたら会社とかでみんなと仲良くなれる気がします。どうでしょうか？個人の意見でございます。
I often see people wearing these in studios, so I feel like if you wear one, you might become closer with people at work or school. What do you think? Just my personal opinion!
そして1泊お泊まりいただけますの！ですが、これ記念ボイス、なんとASMRとなっております！こちら記念ボイスのASMRボイスは
And I'll take a night to stay over! But wait, the commemorative voice pack is an ASMR voice! The commemorative ASMR voice is...
デート帰りの膝枕ボイス！膝枕ボイス！おーい！
A lap-pillow voice after a date! Lap-pillow voice! Oh man!
こちら価格が3,000となっておりますが、お値段以上のものだとポルカは思っております。
The price is set at 3,000, but Polka believes it's worth way more than the price.
なんてこんな、あーやもう、言えない、もううん、言葉に表せないけど、最近ちょっとポルカセブン、オフポルカセブンなかったよなってって感じの人は
Like, oh man, I can't even put it into words, but for those who felt like we haven't had much "Polka Sevens" or "Off-Polka Sevens" lately,
これ絶対聞くとね、めちゃくちゃ良く眠れると思う。本当に。あのね、すごいワガママ言って少し長く撮ってしまいましたので、ちょっとお値段がね、高くなってしまったんですが、その分の価値が絶対にあると思うので絶対に買ってくれよな。
listening to this will definitely help you sleep so well. Truly. I was a bit selfish and made it a little long, so the price went up, but I'm certain it's totally worth it, so please definitely buy it!
はい、そして気になる販売期間となっておりますこちら本日2022年1月30日から2022年の3月7日そしてこちら6時
Yes, and regarding the sales period: starting today, January 30, 2022, until March 7, 2022, and until 6:00...
あのTP… 嘘じゃん
Oh, TP... wait, no.
ジャパン、ジャパンタイム…今のカットで
Japan, Japan time... cut that part.
ジャパンタイム、ジャパンタイム…
Japan time, Japan time...
今のカットで、J…JP…
Cut that part, J... JP...
日本時間の6時まで、18時までとなっております。
available until 6:00 PM, 18:00 Japan time.
グッズはすべてこちら受注販売商品となっておりますので、
All goods are made-to-order items,
まあ、焦らずお買い求めください！
so please take your time ordering!
というわけで、尾丸ポルカがお送りしましたホロバックプロデュース、
And with that, Omaru Polka presented the Holo Bag Produce,
そして尾丸ポルカ生誕祭のライブ、楽しかったでしょうか？
and the Omaru Polka birthday live. Did you enjoy it?
楽しめえたならんなによりです。
I hope you enjoyed it.
今日来ていただいたゲストというか、もう一生のチームの仲間たちって感じなんだけど、
As for today's guests—more like lifelong teammates—
ポルカがやりたいよーにやらしていただいて、そして見てる皆さんもやりたいよーにやってるポルカを
I got to do whatever I wanted, and everyone watching let me do my thing
なんとなく、ぬるまー…く、濃いめで見てくれたかなと思っております。
in your own warm... yet intense way, I suppose.
やりたいこと少しはまたやれたかなと思っております。
I feel like I was able to do a bit of what I wanted.
それではそれでは、ありがとうございましたー！
Well then, thank you very much!